Here is a metaphor that highlights the importance of helping others.
A farmer grows lots of fine corn on his farm.
Every year he reports his corn to a competition for the area's best crops.
And every year he wins.
One year he was interviewed by a reporter who wanted to find out the secret behind the award -winning corn.
The answer made the reporter very astonished.
The farmer told me that he always shared the grain with his neighbors.
"But how can you give the grain to your competitors"
The reporter asked.
"Oh," the farmer said.
"It's not that hard to understand"
How you can help others feel safe
Encourage ideas from others and try to avoid getting into a defensive position.
When others make mistakes on training or competition, the most common thing is to do nothing special and just drive on.
However, some choose to bark at the person who made the mistake.
However, given how people work in groups, we need to be careful about how we choose to act on the faults of others.
In fact, most people feel insecure when someone bark at them.
Which often leads to more mistakes.
So the opposite of the effect they really want.
That being said, it is not always wrong to bark or mark when someone makes violations.
Especially not when it comes to things that the person can actually control.
It is, for example, under the person's control how it behaves towards its teammates.